Anthony Rosman

Frontend web developer | Javascript | Typescript | React

Venezuela

■ anthonyrosman20@gmail.com

+584249253164

in anthonyrosman

D3press3dd

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Frontend web developer, QUANTUMX

May 2022 – present

- Develop multi-client and multi-language SAAS solutions.
- Mentorships and pair programming with part of the team
- Propose and defend tolos to use in frontend
- Collaborate in the implementation of standardizzed UI components that allow speeding up the construction and maintenance of use interfaces
- Codify standardized UI components that speed up the construction and maintenance of solutions
- Solve implementation challenges of advance UI components
- Participate in design and architecture

Frontend web developer with React, FREELANCER.COM

Jan 2020 – May 2022

Creation and maintenance of software on the freelance.com platform with a good reputation and experience, more than 100 websites created under quality standards.

Frontend web developer, CROING

Mar 2019 – Dec 2020

Participated in various company projects such as creating modules for web promotions for companies such as Sprite, Adidas and Reebok, located in Argentina and Chile.

Frontend Web developer, EZIA

Feb 2018 – Feb 2019

Participate in various projects of the company performing tasks such as code documentation and front-end development.

Fullstack developer, PHARMACOLOGY UNIVERSITY / E-COMMERCE

Jan 2017 – Jan 2018

 Analysis, Design and Development of an Information System under Web environment, Database Manager in PostgreSQL, development environment in: HTML, PHP 5, JavaScript, JQuery, Documentation, Training and Implementation of the System.

PROFILE

Software Engineer and Front-end developer freelance graduated from Venezuela with **5+ years of experience** building and creating user-friendly websites and web applications, **3 years with React js**, i spend my time on personal projects and learning more about front-end and how to improve my skills.

Always eager to adapt and take on new challenges!

SKILLS

Frontend (HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT, GRAPHQL/LIBRARIES-REACT, REDUX/TESTING-JEST, PLAYWRIGHT/CSS PREPROCESSORS-SASS, LESS/DESKTOP FIRST Y MOBILE FIRST/AGILE METHODOLOGIES & SCRUM)

EDUCATION

Ludovico Silva University, *Software Engineer* Graduated as a software and computer engineer

Feb 2010 – Jun 2016 Monagas, Venezuela

Unare III Institure, Bachelor of Science

Sep 2005 – Jan 2010

Graduate as bachelor of science